I was going to pull out him.
Screwing my tires.
So I said that I thought I said it in my mind.
Like you can't just pull off.
I didn't pull off.
Oh, nice, nice.
This is the eighth instant.
That looks something done for the foremost tires.
Oh, my throat.
A second one.
Okay.
My throat is so sticky.
Are we ready?
We're going to call over the refrigerator meeting that we might need.
It's fussy toady, forty, fifty, fifty, and a time.
It was the invocation of my pastor at 1st December of God Church David Jackson, David, thanks for being here tonight.
That's all we want to put.
Question something about how we just thank you that we can gather here and govern ourselves forward.
But we seek your wisdom, seek your hand upon us,
give us full knowledge to make rise decisions for all the people's Lord,
and may you guide us and lead us, may we come to agreement,
may we get along with each other or may we show the Lord of Jesus Christ in your name, amen.
Amen.
Father, would you like to question please?
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands, one nation under God,
indivisible with liberty and justice.
Thank you.
I'm first public input and unscheduled personal appearances are on the audience
and it's it wishes to address the authority on any of the agenda items.
There will be not-on-five, it's consent agenda staff is recommending item six to eight for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions with intercane emotion.
Motion approved by.
And a second.
Second, roll call, please.
Johnson.
Mr.
I.
I'm nine as new business and new business.
Council members are dean.
I intend to staff reports then you packet.
You know, available for questions if they're already.
I've got a run by a local digital investment law, forget it.
I talked to her.
I'd say imagine me.
I'm just about a few days ago about, I've got some inquiries about our boat survey.
Could you have that as a metaphor of public?
Actually, we've gotten a copy of the boat survey.
I think we're just about ready to roll on at that time.
The target is when to give us an idea.
I just took a look at it a little bit ago.
We have our rough draft.
Then we had staff look at it.
And so the ETC will take it out to a small number of citizens just to see if they have any questions about it.
And then they will send it out to the large group.
They would like to try it out with a small sample size to make sure everybody understands the questions.
And then every that there's no things that they miss.
And then they'll send it out to the large group.
A long process.
We talked about Tyler.
And they think about a month.
About a month?
Yes sir.
And we're talking about money into this month getting it out.
We're talking about small group.
To this small group.
And then even maybe the first of February like to the large group.
So that's where some issues that day.
If I remember.
You know, when we were talking, I think the deliverable was in March, okay, it was over there, okay, yeah, that's all I have about making.
Any other questions for staff on the items?
They're being not out of 11 is trustee community announcements in the announcements.
I'm 12 is a gentleman. We have most of your time. We'll see you during.
And second.
Roll out please.
Weston.
I'm Lewis.
I'm Johnson.
I'm Forester.
Hi.